{
    "questionList": [
        {
            "number": 1,
            "question": "Which country has the largest proven oil reserves? (2025)",
            "opt1": "United States",
            "opt2": "Qatar",
            "opt3": "Venezuela",
            "opt4": "Egypt",
            "answer": "Venezuela"
        },

        {
            "number": 2,
            "question": "Which country has the world's coldest continually inhabited community?",
            "opt1": "Greenland",
            "opt2": "Sweden",
            "opt3": "Iceland",
            "opt4": "Russia",
            "answer": "Russia"
        },

        {
            "number": 3,
            "question": "What is Africa's most populated country?",
            "opt1": "South Africa",
            "opt2": "Ghana",
            "opt3": "Nigeria",
            "opt4": "Morocco",
            "answer": "Nigeria"
        },

        {
            "number": 4,
            "question": "Where is K2, Earth's second highest peak?",
            "opt1": "Pakistan",
            "opt2": "United States",
            "opt3": "Nepal",
            "opt4": "Russia",
            "answer": "Pakistan"
        },

        {
            "number": 5,
            "question": "Easter Island is a territory of which country?",
            "opt1": "New Zealand",
            "opt2": "Papua New Guinea",
            "opt3": "Chile",
            "opt4": "Ecuador",
            "answer": "Chile"
        },

        {
            "number": 6,
            "question": "Which country has the world's highest percentage of Buddhists?",
            "opt1": "Cambodia",
            "opt2": "Philippines",
            "opt3": "South Korea",
            "opt4": "India",
            "answer": "Cambodia"
        },

        {
            "number": 7,
            "question": "Which country has the most time zones?",
            "opt1": "United States",
            "opt2": "China",
            "opt3": "France",
            "opt4": "United Kingdom",
            "answer": "France"
        },

        {
            "number": 8,
            "question": "Which country is the only native habitat of the lemur?",
            "opt1": "Madagascar",
            "opt2": "Tanzania",
            "opt3": "India",
            "opt4": "Mozambique",
            "answer": "Madagascar"
        },

        {
            "number": 9,
            "question": "What is considered to be the newest country? (2025)",
            "opt1": "Montenegro",
            "opt2": "Belarus",
            "opt3": "South Sudan",
            "opt4": "Sierra Leone",
            "answer": "South Sudan"
        },

        {
            "number": 10,
            "question": "Which country has the most companies with the largest international revenue?",
            "opt1": "China",
            "opt2": "Saudi Arabia",
            "opt3": "Qatar",
            "opt4": "United States",
            "answer": "United States"
        },

        {
            "number": 11,
            "question": "Which country has the world's longest coastline?",
            "opt1": "United States",
            "opt2": "Russia",
            "opt3": "Canada",
            "opt4": "Austrailia",
            "answer": "Canada"
        },

        {
            "number": 12,
            "question": "The Great Barrier Reef, the world's largest coral reef system, is closest to which country?",
            "opt1": "Indonesia",
            "opt2": "Philippines",
            "opt3": "Russia",
            "opt4": "Austrailia",
            "answer": "Austrailia"
        },

        {
            "number": 13,
            "question": "Of the options, which country is smallest in total territory?",
            "opt1": "Monaco",
            "opt2": "Vatican City",
            "opt3": "Nauru",
            "opt4": "Tuvalu",
            "answer": "Vatican City"
        },

        {
            "number": 14,
            "question": "Which Nordic country has the nickname 'Land of Many Lakes?'",
            "opt1": "Sweden",
            "opt2": "Finland",
            "opt3": "Norway",
            "opt4": "Denmark",
            "answer": "Finland"
        },

        {
            "number": 15,
            "question": "Tuscany, home of Leonardo da Vinci and known for famous wines, is in which country?",
            "opt1": "Spain",
            "opt2": "France",
            "opt3": "Italy",
            "opt4": "Portugal",
            "answer": "Italy"
        },

        {
            "number": 16,
            "question": "Which country is known for its ancient Incan ruins, including Machu Picchu?",
            "opt1": "Peru",
            "opt2": "Bolivia",
            "opt3": "Chile",
            "opt4": "Ecuador",
            "answer": "Peru"
        },

        {
            "number": 17,
            "question": "Which country has the world's strongest currency? (2025)",
            "opt1": "United States",
            "opt2": "United Arab Emirates",
            "opt3": "Kuwait",
            "opt4": "Switzerland",
            "answer": "Kuwait"
        },

        {
            "number": 18,
            "question": "Once visited by George Washington, which country is home of Bajans?",
            "opt1": "Brazil",
            "opt2": "Barbados",
            "opt3": "Dominican Republic",
            "opt4": "Bolivia",
            "answer": "Barbados"
        },

        {
            "number": 19,
            "question": "Which country is located in modern day Persia?",
            "opt1": "Yemen",
            "opt2": "Greece",
            "opt3": "Macedonia",
            "opt4": "Iran",
            "answer": "Iran"
        },

        {
            "number": 20,
            "question": "Which country was known as 'Ceylon' until 1972?",
            "opt1": "Sri Lanka",
            "opt2": "Cyprus",
            "opt3": "Indonesia",
            "opt4": "Laos",
            "answer": "Sri Lanka"
        },

        {
            "number": 21,
            "question": "Kimchi, or spicy fermented cabbage, comes from which country?",
            "opt1": "South Korea",
            "opt2": "Japan",
            "opt3": "Indonesia",
            "opt4": "Taiwan",
            "answer": "South Korea"
        },

        {
            "number": 22,
            "question": "Which country has won the most FIFA World Cups?",
            "opt1": "Argentina",
            "opt2": "Germany",
            "opt3": "Brazil",
            "opt4": "Italy",
            "answer": "Brazil"
        },

        {
            "number": 23,
            "question": "Which country is the home of classical music prodigy Mozart?",
            "opt1": "Italy",
            "opt2": "Germany",
            "opt3": "Czech Republic",
            "opt4": "Austria",
            "answer": "Austria"
        },

        {
            "number": 24,
            "question": "Which country has the 'Chicxulub Crater,' proposed site of the dinosaur extinction?",
            "opt1": "Mexico",
            "opt2": "Canada",
            "opt3": "United States",
            "opt4": "Guatemala",
            "answer": "Mexico"
        },

        {
            "number": 25,
            "question": "Which country partially contains Matterhorn mountain and makes Toblerone chocolate as a result?",
            "opt1": "Canada",
            "opt2": "Denmark",
            "opt3": "Poland",
            "opt4": "Switzerland",
            "answer": "Switzerland"
        },

        {
            "number": 26,
            "question": "Which country has a black and red flag with a star, machete, and cogwheel?",
            "opt1": "Georgia",
            "opt2": "Kyrgyzstan",
            "opt3": "Angola",
            "opt4": "Malawi",
            "answer": "Angola"
        },

        {
            "number": 27,
            "question": "Which country has the oldest tri-color flag in use?",
            "opt1": "Netherlands",
            "opt2": "France",
            "opt3": "Italy",
            "opt4": "Russia",
            "answer": "Netherlands"
        },

        {
            "number": 28,
            "question": "Inspiring the popular puzzle, Hanoi is the capital of what country?",
            "opt1": "Vietnam",
            "opt2": "Singapore",
            "opt3": "Sri Lanka",
            "opt4": "Thailand",
            "answer": "Vietnam"
        },

        {
            "number": 29,
            "question": "Inspiring the coding assignment, which country is known for its rope bridges and Dr. Baas' scholarship work?",
            "opt1": "Bhutan",
            "opt2": "Ethiopia",
            "opt3": "India",
            "opt4": "Nigeria",
            "answer": "Bhutan"
        },

        {
            "number": 30,
            "question": "Which country is known for its strong tradition of lively dance, such as tango?",
            "opt1": "Honduras",
            "opt2": "Mexico",
            "opt3": "Guyana",
            "opt4": "Argentina",
            "answer": "Argentina"
        },

        {
            "number": 31,
            "question": "Which country is known as the birthplace of the Olympics?",
            "opt1": "Italy",
            "opt2": "Greece",
            "opt3": "Russia",
            "opt4": "North Macedonia",
            "answer": "Greece"
        },

        {
            "number": 32,
            "question": "One of the largest lion habitats, the Serengeti region/ecosystem is in which country?",
            "opt1": "Madagascar",
            "opt2": "Zimbabwe",
            "opt3": "Tanzania",
            "opt4": "Mali",
            "answer": "Tanzania"
        },

        {
            "number": 33,
            "question": "Which country has the world's tallest building, the Burj Khalifa?",
            "opt1": "Kuwait",
            "opt2": "Russia",
            "opt3": "China",
            "opt4": "United Arab Emirates",
            "answer": "United Arab Emirates"
        },

        {
            "number": 34,
            "question": "Which country is known for its ancient pyramids and Sphinx?",
            "opt1": "Argentina",
            "opt2": "Peru",
            "opt3": "Egypt",
            "opt4": "Syria",
            "answer": "Egypt"
        },

        {
            "number": 35,
            "question": "Which is the largest African country by land area?",
            "opt1": "Ethiopia",
            "opt2": "Nigeria",
            "opt3": "Algeria",
            "opt4": "Sudan",
            "answer": "Algeria"
        },

        {
            "number": 36,
            "question": "What country is known for its globaly influential pottery and silk goods?",
            "opt1": "Japan",
            "opt2": "Russia",
            "opt3": "South Korea",
            "opt4": "China",
            "answer": "China"
        },

        {
            "number": 37,
            "question": "'Godzilla', a ficticious radioactive monster, originates from which country?",
            "opt1": "Russia",
            "opt2": "China",
            "opt3": "France",
            "opt4": "Japan",
            "answer": "Japan"
        },

        {
            "number": 38,
            "question": "'The Loch Ness Monster,' a mythological lake dweller, originates from where?",
            "opt1": "Denmark",
            "opt2": "Netherlands",
            "opt3": "United Kingdom",
            "opt4": "Belgium",
            "answer": "United Kingdom"
        },

        {
            "number": 39,
            "question": "The ancient wonder and sandstone city of Petra is located in which country?",
            "opt1": "Italy",
            "opt2": "Germany",
            "opt3": "Jordan",
            "opt4": "Iraq",
            "answer": "Jordan"
        },

        {
            "number": 40,
            "question": "Footballer Cristiano Ronaldo (CR7) hails from which country?",
            "opt1": "Spain",
            "opt2": "United Kingdom",
            "opt3": "Portugal",
            "opt4": "Italy",
            "answer": "Portugal"
        },

        {
            "number": 41,
            "question": "Which country has the longest border with Mexico?",
            "opt1": "Guatemala",
            "opt2": "Belize",
            "opt3": "El Salvador",
            "opt4": "Honduras",
            "answer": "Guatemala"
        },

        {
            "number": 42,
            "question": "Which country owns the famous Galápagos islands?",
            "opt1": "Ecuador",
            "opt2": "Guatemala",
            "opt3": "Costa Rica",
            "opt4": "Peru",
            "answer": "Ecuador"
        },

        {
            "number": 43,
            "question": "Which Caribbean country is known for its classic cars and cigars?",
            "opt1": "Haiti",
            "opt2": "Dominican Republic",
            "opt3": "Jamaica",
            "opt4": "Cuba",
            "answer": "Cuba"
        },

        {
            "number": 44,
            "question": "Sprinter Usain Bolt hails from which country?",
            "opt1": "Haiti",
            "opt2": "Dominican Republic",
            "opt3": "Jamaica",
            "opt4": "Cuba",
            "answer": "Jamaica"
        },

        {
            "number": 45,
            "question": "Nelson Mandela was the president of which country?",
            "opt1": "Lesotho",
            "opt2": "South Africa",
            "opt3": "Ghana",
            "opt4": "Ethiopia",
            "answer": "South Africa"
        },

        {
            "number": 46,
            "question": "The ancient city of Carthage is in which current country?",
            "opt1": "Morocco",
            "opt2": "Egypt",
            "opt3": "Greece",
            "opt4": "Tunisia",
            "answer": "Tunisia"
        },

        {
            "number": 47,
            "question": "Marathon runner Eliud Kipchoge hails from which country?",
            "opt1": "Nigeria",
            "opt2": "Morocco",
            "opt3": "Ghana",
            "opt4": "Kenya",
            "answer": "Kenya"
        },

        {
            "number": 48,
            "question": "What is the largest landlocked country?",
            "opt1": "Lesotho",
            "opt2": "Belarus",
            "opt3": "Kazakhstan",
            "opt4": "Algeria",
            "answer": "Kazakhstan"
        },

        {
            "number": 49,
            "question": "What is the largest archipelagic country?",
            "opt1": "Philippines",
            "opt2": "Indonesia",
            "opt3": "Dominican Republic",
            "opt4": "Jamaica",
            "answer": "Indonesia"
        },

        {
            "number": 50,
            "question": "What country is has the world's coldest capital along with a high population of snow leopards?",
            "opt1": "Russia",
            "opt2": "Sweden",
            "opt3": "Canada",
            "opt4": "Mongolia",
            "answer": "Mongolia"
        }

    ]
}
	